Guide to the Alumni Records Office, Yale University, Records of Alumni from the Classes of 1701-1978
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Sheffield Scientific School and Engineering, Series II
  - 1900 St-Z - x1900 A-M (Box 687)
  - x1900 N-Z - 1901 A-Cond (Box 688)
  - 1901 Cone-Kn (Box 689)
  - 1901 Ko-Warm (Box 690)
  - 1901 Warn-Z - 1902 A-Bag (Box 691)
  - 1902 Bar-Hic (Box 692)
  - 1902 Hid-Sa (Box 693)
  - 1902 Sb-Z - x1902 A-Z (Box 694)
  - 1903 A-Bq (Box 695)
  - 1903 Br-Ea (Box 696)
  - 1903 Eb-Me (Box 697)
  - 1903 Mf-Wh (Box 698)
  - 1903 Wi-Z - x1903 A-Z (Box 699)
  - 1904 A-Cn (Box 700)
  - 1904 Co-J (Box 701)
  - 1904 K-S (Box 702)
  - 1904 T-Z - x1904 A-M (Box 703)
  - x1904 N-Z - 1905 A-B (Box 704)
  - 1905 C-J (Box 705)
  - 1905 K-So (Box 706)
  - 1905 Sp-Z - x1905 A-O (Box 707)
  - x1905 P-Z - 1906 A-B (Box 708)
  - 1906 C-H (Box 709)
  - 1906 I-R (Box 710)
  - 1906 S-Z - x1906 A-C (Box 711)
  - x1906 D-Z - 1907 A (Box 712)
  - 1907 B-Cl (Box 713)
  - 1907 Cm-I (Box 714)
  - 1907 J-P (Box 715)
  - 1907 Q-Wh (Box 716)
  - 1907 Wi-Z - x1907 A-T (Box 717)
  - x1907 U-Z - 1908 A-B (Box 718)
  - 1908 C-G (Box 719)
  - 1908 H-L (Box 720)
  - 1908 M-Q (Box 721)
  - 1908 R-V (Box 722)
  - 1908 W-Z - x1908 A-C (Box 723)
  - x1908 D-Z (Box 724)
  - 1909 A-D (Box 725)
  - 1909 E-L (Box 726)
  - 1909 M-T (Box 727)
  - 1909 U-Z - x1909 A-H (Box 728)
  - x1909 I-Z - 1910 General (Box 729)
  - 1910 A-Cham (Box 730)
  - 1910 Chan-Has (Box 731)
  - 1910 Hat-L (Box 732)
  - 1910 M-R (Box 733)
  - 1910 S-W (Box 734)
  - 1910 X-Z x1910 A-O (Box 735)
  - x1910 P-Z - 1911 A (Box 736)
  - 1911 B-Cl (Box 737)
  - 1911 Cm-G (Box 738)
  - 1911 H-L (Box 739)
  - 1911 M-P (Box 740)
  - 1911 Q-T (Box 741)
  - 1911 U-Z - 1911 A-G (Box 742)
  - x1911 H-Z (Box 743)
  - 1912 A-Be (Box 744)
  - 1912 Bf-Cl (Box 745)
  - 1912 Cm-E (Box 746)
  - 1912 F-Hu (Box 747)
  - 1912 Hv-Mc (Box 748)
  - 1912 Md-P (Box 749)
  - 1912 Q-Sm (Box 750)
  - 1912 S-Z (Box 751)
  - x1912 A-R (Box 752)
  - x1912 S-Z (Box 753)
  - 1913 A-B (Box 754)
  - 1913 C-E (Box 755)
  - 1913 F-Hi (Box 756)
  - 1913 Ho-Ma (Box 757)
  - 1913 Me-R (Box 758)
  - 1913 S-To (Box 759)
  - 1913 T-Z - x1913 A-F (Box 760)
  - x1913 G-Z - 1914 General (Box 761)
  - 1914 A-B (Box 762)
  - 1914 C-Fal (Box 763)
  - 1914 Fam-H (Box 764)
  - 1914 I-O (Box 765)
  - 1914 P-Sm (Box 766)
  - 1914 Sn-W (Box 767)
  - 1914 Y-Z - x1914 A-R (Box 768)
  - x1914 S-Z - 1915 A-Ba (Box 769)
  - 1915 Bb-Cor (Box 770)
  - 1915 Cos-Ha (Box 771)
  - 1915 Hb-Le (Box 772)
  - 1915 Lf-N (Box 773)
  - 1915 O-Sm (Box 774)
  - 1915 Sn-Z (Box 775)
  - x1915 A-N (Box 776)
  - x1915 P-Z - 1916 A-Bea (Box 777)
  - 1916 Beb-E (Box 778)
  - 1916 F-Ke (Box 779)
  - 1916 Kf-Res (Box 780)
  - 1916 Ret-S (Box 781)
  - 1916 T-Z (Box 782)
  - x1916 A-S (Box 783)
  - x1916 T-Z - 1917 A-Buc (Box 784)
  - 1917 Bud-E (Box 785)
  - 1917 F-K (Box 786)
  - 1917 L-P (Box 787)
  - 1917 Q-V (Box 788)
  - 1917 W-Z - x1917 A-G (Box 789)
  - x1917 H-Z (Box 790)
  - 1918 A-D (Box 791)
  - 1918 E-L (Box 792)
  - 1918 M-Sk (Box 793)
  - 1918 Sl-Z - x1918 A-Be (Box 794)
  - x1918 Bf-H (Box 795)
  - x1918 I-P (Box 796)
  - x1918 Q-We (Box 797)
  - x1918 Wf-Z - 1919 A-D (Box 798)
  - 1919 E-L (Box 799)
  - 1919 M-S (Box 800)
  - 1919 T-Z - x1919 A-E (Box 801)
  - x1919 F-R (Box 802)
  - x1919 S-Z - 1920 A-Ca (Box 803)
  - 1920 Cb-Ho (Box 804)
  - 1920 Hp-Q (Box 805)
  - 1920 R-Wa (Box 806)
  - 1920 Wb-Z - x1920 A-Ma (Box 807)
  - x1920 Mb-Z -1921 A-Ba (Box 808)
  - 1921 Bb-D (Box 809)
  - 1921 E-I (Box 810)
  - 1921 J-O (Box 811)
  - 1921 P-Ste (Box 812)
  - 1921 Stf-Z - x1921 A-C (Box 813)
  - x1921 D-Z (Box 814)
  - 1922 A-I (Box 815)
  - 1922 J-Z - x1922 A-R (Box 816)
  - x1922 S-Z - 1923 A-D (Box 817)
  - 1923 E-M (Box 818)
  - 1923 N-We (Box 819)
  - 1923 Wf-Z - x1923 A-H (Box 820)
  - x1923 I-Z (Box 821)
  - 1924 A-B (Box 822)
  - 1924 C-G (Box 823)
  - 1924 H-Mi (Box 824)
  - 1924 Mj-V (Box 825)
  - 1924 W-Z - x1924 A-R (Box 826)
  - x1924 S-Z - 1925 A-B (Box 827)
  - 1925 C-Ha (Box 828)
  - 1925 Hb-Ne (Box 829)
  - 1925 Nf-V (Box 830)
  - 1925 W-Z - x1925 A-Z (Box 831)
  - 1926 A-C (Box 832)
  - 1926 D-Hoy (Box 833)
  - 1926 Huf-M (Box 834)
  - 1926 N-T (Box 835)
  - 1926 U-Z - x1926 A-M (Box 836)
  - x1926 N-Z - 1927 A-Bow (Box 837)
  - 1927 Bow-F (Box 838)
  - 1927 G-L (Box 839)
  - 1927 M-R (Box 840)
  - 1927 S-Z - x1927 A-H (Box 841)
  - x1927 I-Z - 1928 A (Box 842)
  - 1928 B-D (Box 843)
  - 1928 E-Ke (Box 844)
  - 1928 Ki-R (Box 845)
  - 1928 S-Z (Box 846)
  - x1928 A-Z - 1929 A (Box 847)
  - 1929 B-F (Box 848)
  - 1929 G-M (Box 849)
  - 1929 N-W (Box 850)
  - 1929 W-Z - x1929 A-Z (Box 851)
  - 1930 A-C (Box 852)
  - 1930 D-K (Box 853)
  - 1930 L-Q (Box 854)
  - 1930 R-Z - x1930 A-B (Box 855)
  - x1930 C-Z (Box 856)
  - 1931 A-E (Box 857)
  - 1931 F-Mc (Box 858)
  - 1931 Ma-V (Box 859)
  - 1931 W-Z - x1931 A-Z (Box 860)
  - 1932 A-F (Box 861)
  - 1932 G-P (Box 862)
  - 1932 R-Z (Box 863)
  - x1932 A-Z (Box 864)
  - 1933 A-Gi (Box 865)
  - 1933 Go-P (Box 866)
  - 1933 Q-Z (Box 867)
  - x1933 A-Z - 1934 A-Ba (Box 868)
  - 1934 Be-K (Box 869)
  - 1934 L-T (Box 870)
  - 1934 U-Z - x1934 A-Z (Box 871)
  - 1935 A-G (Box 872)
  - 1935 H-S (Box 873)
  - 1935 T-Z - x1935 A-Z (Box 874)
  - 1936 A-H (Box 875)
  - 1936 I-T (Box 876)
  - 1936 U-Z - 1937 A-Be (Box 877)
  - 1937 Bi-H (Box 878)
  - 1937 I-V (Box 879)
  - 1937 W-Z - 1938 A-C (Box 880)
  - 1938 D-Mc (Box 881)
  - 1938 M-Wh (Box 882)
  - 1938 Wi-Z - 1939 A-C (Box 883)
  - 1939 D-Mc (Box 884)
  - 1939 M-Z (Box 885)
  - x1939 A-Z - 1940 A-Di (Box 886)
  - 1940 Do-Mc (Box 887)
  - 1940 M-Wh (Box 888)
  - 1940 Wi-Z - 1941 A-D (Box 889)
  - 1941 E-R (Box 890)
  - 1941 S-Z - 1942 A-Be (Box 891)
  - 1942 Bi-H (Box 892)
  - 1942 I-Ti (Box 893)
  - 1942 To-Z - x1942 A-Z (Box 894)
  - 1943 A-Hi (Box 895)
  - 1943 Ho-Sch (Box 896)
  - 1943 Sci-Z - x1943 A-Z (Box 897)
  - 1944 A-F (Box 898)
  - 1944 G-Mon (Box 899)
  - 1944 Moo-Z - x1944 A-D (Box 900)
  - x1944 E-Z - 1945 A-G (Box 901)
  - 1945 H-R (Box 902)
  - 1945 S-Z - x1945 A-R (Box 903)
  - x1945 S-Z - 1945 We, Ws: A-F (Box 904)
  - 1945 We, Ws: G-Man (Box 905)
  - 1945 We, Ws: Mar-Mi (Box 905A)
  - 1945 We, Ws: Mo-Z (Box 906)
  - x1945 We, Ws: A-Z - 1946 A-C (Box 907)
  - 1946 D-P (Box 908)
  - 1946 Q-Z - 1946 Mar E&S: A-Z (Box 909)
  - 1947 A-K (Box 910)
  - 1947 L-Wel (Box 911)
  - 1947 Wem-Z - x1948 A-J (Box 912)
  - x1948 K-Z - 1949 A-L (Box 913)
  - 1949 M-Z - 1950 (Box 914)
  - D. Eng 36-49, M. Eng 36-46 (Box 915)
  - M. Eng 47-49, all other degrees (1) (Box 916)
  - All other degrees (2) (Box 917)
- Medicine, Series III
  Each of the Classes 1814 to 1949 is divided into two sections for graduates and non-graduates. Files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 918-939]
  For the Classes 1950-1954, files for non-graduates are filed together according to their class. [Box 939]
  For the Classes 1950-1954, files for students receiving special degrees (Special Degree) or having special status are filed as a separate group. [Box 940]
  Files for students graduating from 1918 to 1949 with the Master of Public Health (M.P.H.) are filed as a separate group. Non-graduate files are kept in a different section. [Boxes 941-942]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954) of the Master of Public Health Program (E.P.H.) are filed together. [Box 942]
  Files for students graduating from 1920-1949 with a Doctorate of Public Health (D.P.H.) are filed separately. Non-graduate files are kept in a different section. [Box 942]
  Files for non-graduate public health students, regardless of degree (Non-graduate M.P.H. and D.P.H.), are filed together for the years 1920 to 1949. [Box 943]
  - 1814-x1872 (Box 918)
  - 1873-1883 (Box 919)
  - 1884-x1892 (Box 920)
  - 1893-x1896 (Box 921)
  - 1897-x1898 (Box 922)
  - 1899-x1902 A-O (Box 923)
  - x1902 P-Z - x1904 A-Z (Box 924)
  - 1905-1907 A-M (Box 925)
  - 1907 N-Z - 1909 A-Z (Box 926)
  - x1909-1911 A-Z (Box 927)
  - x1911 A-Z - x1916 A-Z (Box 928)
  - 1917-x1923 (Box 929)
  - 1924-x1925 (Box 930)
  - 1926-x1927 (Box 931)
  - 1928-x1929 (Box 932)
  - 1930-x1931 (Box 933)
  - 1932-x1934 (Box 934)
  - 1935-1937 A-F (Box 935)
  - 1937 G-Z - 1940 A-O (Box 936)
  - 1940 P-Z - 1943 A-M (Box 937)
  - 1943 N-Z - 1946, includes x (Box 938)
  - 1947-1954 (Box 939)
  - Special M A-Z (Box 940)
  - MPH 1918-1942 (Box 941)
  - MPH 1943-1954, DPH General, 1920-1948 (Box 942)
  - DPH x1935-1949 (Box 943)
- Law, Series IV
  Each of the Classes 1829-1949 is divided into two sections for graduate and non-graduate files. Files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 944-993]
  Files for students graduating from 1905 to 1917 with the B.L.C. are filed as a separate group. [Box 993]
  Files for students graduating from 1887 to 1949 with the LL.M. are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 993-995]
  Files for students graduating from 1895 to 1934 with the D.C.L. are filed as a separate group. [Box 995]
  Files for students graduating from 1912 to 1924 with the J.D. are filed as a separate group. [Box 995]
  Files for students graduating from 1925 to 1950 with the J.S.D. are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 995-996]
  Files for students graduating from 1925 to 1950 with the special law degree (Special Degree) or special status are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 996-998]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed together according to their class. [Boxes 999-1000]
  - 1829-1874 (Box 944)
  - x1874-1879 (Box 945)
  - x1879-1883 (Box 946)
  - x1883-x1885 (Box 947)
  - 1886-1889 A-B (Box 948)
  - 1889 C-Z - 1891 A-L (Box 949)
  - 1891 M-Z - 1893 A-L (Box 950)
  - 1893 M-Z - 1894 A-Z (Box 951)
  - x1894 A-Z - 1895 A-M (Box 952)
  - 1895 N-Z - x1896 N-L (Box 953)
  - x1896 M-Z - 1897 A-Z (Box 954)
  - x1897-1899 A-S (Box 955)
  - 1899 T-Z - x1900 A-Z (Box 956)
  - 1901-1902 A-S (Box 957)
  - 1902 T-Z - 1903 A-M (Box 958)
  - 1903 N-Z - 1904 A-Z (Box 959)
  - x1904-1905 A-L (Box 960)
  - 1905 M-Z - 1906 A-N (Box 961)
  - 1906 O-Z - 1907 A-U (Box 962)
  - 1907 V-Z - 1908 A-L (Box 963)
  - 1908 M-Z - x1908 A-Z (Box 964)
  - 1909 A-V (Box 965)
  - 1909 W-Z - 1910 A-K (Box 966)
  - 1910 L-Z - x1910 A-K (Box 967)
  - x1910 L-Z - 1911 A-L (Box 968)
  - 1911 M-Z (Box 969)
  - x1911 A-Z - 1912 A-H (Box 970)
  - 1912 I-Z - x1914 (Box 971)
  - 1915-x1917 (Box 972)
  - 1918-1921 A-E (Box 973)
  - 1921 F-Z - 1923 A-K (Box 974)
  - 1923 L-Z - 1924 A-S (Box 975)
  - 1924 T-Z - 1925 A-Z (Box 976)
  - x1925-1927 A-B (Box 977)
  - 1927 C-Z - x1927 A-M (Box 978)
  - x1927 P-Z - 1928 A-Z (Box 979)
  - x1928 A-Z - 1929 A-Z (Box 980)
  - x1929-1931 A-C (Box 981)
  - 1931 D-Z - 1932 A-R (Box 982)
  - 1932 S-Z - 1934 A-H (Box 983)
  - 1934 I-Z - 1936 A-E (Box 984)
  - 1936 F-Z - 1937 A-L (Box 985)
  - 1934 M-Z - x1938 (Box 986)
  - 1939 A-Z - 1940 A-F (Box 987)
  - 1940 G-Z - 1941 A-L (Box 988)
  - 1941 M-Z - x1942 A-Z (Box 989)
  - 1943-1946 A-G (Box 990)
  - 1946 H-ZS - 1947 A-S (Box 991)
  - 1947 T-Z - 1949 A-S (Box 992)
  - 1949 T-Z, B.L.C. 1905-1917, LLM. 1877-1906 (Box 993)
  - LLM. 1907-1933 (Box 994)
  - LLM. 1936-1949, D.C.L. 1895-1934, J.D. 1912-1924, J.S.D. 1925-1927 (Box 995)
  - J.S.D. 1928-1950, Special Law A-B (Box 996)
  - Special Law C-K (Box 997)
  - Special Law L-Z (Box 998)
  - 1950-1952 (all degrees combined) (Box 999)
  - 1953-1954 (all degrees combined) (Box 1000)
- Divinity, Series V
  Each of the Classes 1829-1949 is divided into two sections for graduate and non-graduate files. Files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 1001-1040]
  Files for students graduating from 1940 to 1949 with the M.S.T. are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 1041 and 1041A]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed together according to their class. [Box 1041]
  Files for students (1950-1954) with a special divinity degree or status are filed as a separate group. [Box 1041]
  - x1829-1876 (Box 1001)
  - 1877-1880 (Box 1002)
  - 1881-1884 A-K (Box 1003)
  - 1884 L-Z - 1886 A-Z (Box 1004)
  - x1886-1889 A-N (Box 1005)
  - 1889 O-Z - 1891 A-K (Box 1006)
  - 1891 L-Z - x1892 (Box 1007)
  - 1893-1894 (Box 1008)
  - x1894-1896 A-D (Box 1009)
  - 1896 E-Z - x1897 (Box 1010)
  - 1898-x1899 (Box 1011)
  - 1900-1902 A-R (Box 1012)
  - 1902 S-Z - 1904 A-M (Box 1013)
  - 1904 N-Z - 1906 A-O (Box 1014)
  - 1906 P-Z - 1909 A-M (Box 1015)
  - 1909 N-Z -1911 A-Z (Box 1016)
  - x1911 A-Z - 1914 A-J (Box 1017)
  - 1914 K-Z - 1916 A-P (Box 1018)
  - 1916 Q-Z - x1917 A-Z (Box 1019)
  - 1918-x1919 (Box 1020)
  - 1920-1921 A-S (Box 1021)
  - 1921 T-Z - 1923 A-B (Box 1022)
  - 1923 C-Z - 1924 A-E (Box 1023)
  - 1924 F-Z - 1925 A-G (Box 1024)
  - 1925 H-Z - x1925 A-Z (Box 1025)
  - 1926-x1926 (Box 1026)
  - 1927-x1927 (Box 1027)
  - 1928-x1928 A-H (Box 1028)
  - x1928 I-Z - x1929 A-J (Box 1029)
  - x1929 K-Z - 1931 A-C (Box 1030)
  - 1931 D-Z - 1932 A-L (Box 1031)
  - 1932 M-Z - x1933 A-Z (Box 1032)
  - 1934 A-Z - x1935 A-Z (Box 1033)
  - 1936 A-Z - 1937 A-H (Box 1034)
  - 1937 I-Z - x1939 A-H (Box 1035)
  - 1939 I-Z - x1940 A-Z (Box 1036)
  - 1941 A-Z - 1942 A-K (Box 1037)
  - 1942 L-Z - 1944 A-Z (Box 1038)
  - x1944-1946 (Box 1039)
  - 1947-1949 (Box 1040)
  - MST 1940-1954, Ex Sp.D A-Z (Box 1041)
  - Ex Sp.D A-Z (Box 1041A)
- Graduate School, Series VI
  Files for all Ph.D. graduates (1861-1949) are filed as a separate group. Files for non-graduates of the graduate school are in a different section. [Boxes 1042-1067]
  Files for all M.A. graduates (1877-1949) are filed as a separate group. Files for non-graduates of the graduate school are in a different section. [Boxes 1067-1084]
  Files for all M.S. graduates (1899-1949) are filed as a separate group. Files for non-graduates of the graduate school are in a different section. [Boxes 1084-1088]
  Files for all non-graduates of the graduate school (1813x-1949x), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed as a group, separate from their class. [Boxes 1088-1113]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed together according to year. [Boxes 1114-1116]
  - Ph.D. 1861-1895 (Box 1042)
  - Ph.D. 1896-1901 (Box 1043)
  - Ph.D. 1902-1904 (Box 1044)
  - Ph.D. 1905-1909 A-D (Box 1045)
  - Ph.D. 1909 E-Z - 1912 (Box 1046)
  - Ph.D. 1913-1916 A-L (Box 1047)
  - Ph.D. 1916 M-Z - 1920 A-M (Box 1048)
  - Ph.D. 1920 N-Z - 1922 (Box 1049)
  - Ph.D. 1923-1925 A-F (Box 1050)
  - Ph.D. 1925 G-Z - 1926 (Box 1051)
  - Ph.D. 1927-1928 A-Sc (Box 1052)
  - Ph.D. 1928 Sh-Z - 1929 (Box 1053)
  - Ph.D. 1930-1931 A-G (Box 1054)
  - Ph.D. 1931 H-Z - 1932 A-L (Box 1055)
  - Ph.D. 1932 M-Z - 1933 A-L (Box 1056)
  - Ph.D. 1933 M-Z - 1934 A-M (Box 1057)
  - Ph.D. 1934 N-Z - 1935 A-R (Box 1058)
  - Ph.D. 1935 S-Z - 1936 (Box 1059)
  - Ph.D. 1937 (Box 1060)
  - Ph.D. 1938-1939 A-G (Box 1061)
  - Ph.D. 1939 H-Z - 1940 A-L (Box 1062)
  - Ph.D. 1940 M-Z - 1941 A-L (Box 1063)
  - Ph.D. 1941 M-Z - 1942 (Box 1064)
  - Ph.D. 1943-1946 A-E (Box 1065)
  - Ph.D. 1946 F-Z - 1949 A-N (Box 1066)
  - Ph.D. 1949 O-Z, M.A. 1877 - 1901 A-T (Box 1067)
  - M.A. 1901 U-Z - 1904 A-L (Box 1068)
  - M.A. 1904 M-Z - 1907 A-L (Box 1069)
  - M.A. 1907 M-Z - 1909 A-L (Box 1070)
  - M.A. 1909 M-Z - 1911 A-F (Box 1071)
  - M.A. 1911 H-Z - 1912 A-S (Box 1072)
  - M.A. 1912 T-Z - 1919 (Box 1073)
  - M.A. 1920-1923 A-S (Box 1074)
  - M.A. 1923 T-Z - 1926 (Box 1075)
  - M.A. 1927-1928 (Box 1076)
  - M.A. 1929-1932 A-F (Box 1077)
  - M.A. 1932 G-Z - 1936 A-N (Box 1078)
  - M.A. 1936 P-Z - 1941 A-S (Box 1079)
  - M.A. 1941 T-Z - 1942 (Box 1080)
  - M.A. 1943-1944 (Box 1081)
  - M.A. 1945-1947 A-J (Box 1082)
  - M.A. 1947 K-Z - 1949 A-H (Box 1083)
  - M.A. 1949 J-Z, M.S. 1899-1923 (Box 1084)
  - M.S. 1924-1928 A-G (Box 1085)
  - M.S. 1928 H-Z - 1931 (Box 1086)
  - M.S. 1932-1943 A-D (Box 1087)
  - M.S. 1943 E-Z - 1949 (all) x1813-x1877 A-E (Box 1088)
  - x1877 H-Z - x1895 A-K (Box 1089)
  - x1895 P-Z - x1902 A-P (Box 1090)
  - x1902 R-Z - x1907 A-C (Box 1091)
  - x1907 D-Z - x1911 (Box 1092)
  - x1912-x1915 (Box 1093)
  - x1916-x1919 (Box 1094)
  - x1922 A-C (Box 1095)
  - x1922 D-Z - x1923 A-O (Box 1096)
  - x1923 P-Z - x1924 A-S (Box 1097)
  - x1924 T-Z - x1925 (Box 1098)
  - x1926 (Box 1099)
  - x1927 (Box 1100)
  - x1928 (Box 1101)
  - x1929-x1930 A-B (Box 1102)
  - x1930 C-Z - x1931 A-C (Box 1103)
  - x1931 D-Z - x1932 A-C (Box 1104)
  - x1932 D-Z - x1933 A-C (Box 1105)
  - x1933 D-Z - x1934 A-J (Box 1106)
  - x1934 K-Z - x1936 A-G (Box 1107)
  - x1936 H-Z - x1937 (Box 1108)
  - x1938-1939 A-H (Box 1109)
  - x1939 J-Z - x1940 (Box 1110)
  - x1941-1942 (Box 1111)
  - x1943-x1946 A-O (Box 1112)
  - x1946 P-Z - x1952 (Box 1113)
  - 1950-1951 (Box 1114)
  - 1951 P-Z, 1952, 1953 A-M (Box 1115)
  - 1953 N-Z, 1954 A-Z (Box 1116)
- Nursing, Series VII
  For the Classes 1926 to 1949, each year is divided into two alphabetical sections for graduate and non-graduate files. Files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 1117-1126]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954) are filed together according to year. [Box 1126]
  Files for students (1950-1954) with a special nursing degree or status are filed as a separate group. [Box 1127]
  - 1926-x1930 A-MacK (Box 1117)
  - 1930 MacM-Z - 1932 A-S (Box 1118)
  - 1932 T-Z - 1934 (Box 1119)
  - 1935-1936 (Box 1120)
  - 1937-1939 A-D (Box 1121)
  - 1939 E-Z - 1941 A-H (Box 1122)
  - 1941 I-Z - 1943 (Box 1123)
  - 1944-1945 (Box 1124)
  - 1946-1947 (Box 1125)
  - War 1947-1954 (Box 1126)
  - x Spec. A-Z (Box 1127)
- Honorary Degrees, Series VIII
  For the the years 1702 to 1954, all files are in alphabetical order according year. [Boxes 1128-1150]
  - 1702-1872 (Box 1128)
  - 1873-1893 (Box 1129)
  - 1894-1901 A-Pet (Box 1130)
  - 1901 Pri-Z - 1905 A-E (Box 1131)
  - 1905 G-Z - 1908 (Box 1132)
  - 1909-1911 A-L (Box 1133)
  - 1911 M-Z - 1915 A-T (Box 1134)
  - 1915 W-Z - 1917 A-B (Box 1135)
  - 1917 C-Z - 1918 A-Hoo (Box 1136)
  - 1918 R-Z - 1920 A-Shel (Box 1137)
  - 1920 Spa-Z - 1921 A-C (Box 1138)
  - 1921 D-Z - 1923 A-N (Box 1139)
  - 1923 O-Z - 1925 A-V (Box 1140)
  - 1925 W-Z - 1927 A-B (Box 1141)
  - 1927 C-Z - 1928 A-H (Box 1142)
  - 1928 Har-Z - 1929 A-O (Box 1143)
  - 1929 P-Z - 1931 A-S (Box 1144)
  - 1931 T-Z - 1933 (Box 1145)
  - 1934-1935 A-S (Box 1146)
  - 1935 T-Z - 1938 A-P (Box 1147)
  - 1938 Q-Z - 1942 A-Be (Box 1148)
  - 1942 Bu-Z - 1947 (Box 1149)
  - 1948-1954 (Box 1150)
- Music, Series IX
  Files for students graduating from 1894 to 1949 with the Music B. are filed as a separate group. Files for non-graduates are in a different section. [Boxes 1151-1154]
  Files for students graduating from 1932 to 1949 with the Music M. are filed as a separate group. Files for non-graduates are in a different section. [Box 1154]
  Files for students graduating from 1898 to 1937 with the Certificate in Music (Musc or Cmus) are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 1154-1157]
  Files for all non-graduates of the music school (1901x-1949x), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed as a group, separate from their class. [Boxes 1157-1162]
  Files for students (1901-1949) with a special music degree or status are filed as a separate group. [Box 1162]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed together according to their class. [Box 1163]
  - 1894-1921 Music B. (Box 1151)
  - 1922-1931 Music B. (Box 1152)
  - 1932-1943 Music B. (Box 1153)
  - 1944-1949 Music B., 1932-1949 Music M., 1898-1905 Music (Box 1154)
  - 1906-1920 A-Sa Music (Box 1155)
  - 1920 Sc-Z - 1932 Music (Box 1156)
  - 1933-1937 Music, x1901-x1910 Music (Box 1157)
  - x1911-x1916 A-Gre Music (Box 1158)
  - x1916 Gre-Z - x1924 Music A-H (H-Z) (Box 1159)
  - x1924-x1930 A-L Music (Box 1160)
  - x1930 M-Z - x1939 A-C Music (Box 1161)
  - x1939 D-Z - x1949, x Spec. Music A-Z (Box 1162)
  - 1950-1954 (Box 1163)
- Art & Architecture, Series X
  Files for students graduating from 1942 to 1951 with the Bachelor or Master of Architecture (B. Arch. or M. Arch.) are filed as a group. Files for non-graduates for these years are filed with the non-graduate art students. [Box 1164]
  Files for students graduating from 1887 to 1949 with the Bachelor of Fine Arts (Art, Drama, and Architecture B.F.A.) are filed as a group. Students with concentrations in Painting, Sculpture, and Drama are included up to 1949, but students with a concentration in Architecture are only included up to 1941. Non-graduate files are in a different section. [Boxes 1164-1171]
  Files for students graduating from 1928 to 1949 with miscellaneous degrees (Misc. Degree) in art are filed as a group. [Box 1171]
  Files for students graduating from 1928 to 1949 with the Master of Fine Arts (Art, Drama, and Architecture M.F.A.) are filed as a group. Students with concentrations in Painting, Sculpture, Graphic Design, and Drama are included up to 1949, but students with a concentration in Architecture are only included up to 1941. Students with a doctorate may also be found here. Non-graduate files are in a different section. [Boxes 1172-1173]
  Files for students graduating from 1879 to 1948 with the Certificate of Art (cart or artc) are filed as a separate group. Non-graduate files are in a different section. [Boxes 1174-1176]
  Files for all non-graduate art, architecture, and drama students (1873x-1949x), regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed as a group, separate from their class. [Boxes 1176-1190]
  Files for students (1873-1949) with a special art degree or status are filed as a separate group. [Box 1191]
  Files for all art and architecture students (1950-1954), graduates and non-graduates, regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed together according to year. [Box 1192]
  Files for all drama students (1950-1954), graduates and non-graduates, regardless of degree (All Degrees), are filed together according to year. [Box 1193]
  For an explanation of the codes used for Fine Art degrees, see Appendix.
  - 1942-1951 Arch, 1887-1905 Art (Box 1164)
  - 1906-1924 Art (Box 1165)
  - 1924-1928 A-F Art (Box 1166)
  - 1928 G-Z - 1930 A-S Art (Box 1167)
  - 1930 T-Z - 1933 Art (Box 1168)
  - 1934-1936 Art (Box 1169)
  - 1937-1940 Art (Box 1170)
  - 1941-1949 Art, Misc. Art degrees 1928-1931 (Box 1171)
  - 1941-1949 Art, Misc. Art degrees 1932-1948 (Box 1171A)
  - 1934-1941 Art M.F.A. (Box 1172)
  - 1942-1949 Art M.F.A. (Box 1173)
  - 1879-1906 Artc (Box 1174)
  - 1906-1932 Artc (Box 1175)
  - 1933-1948 Artc, x1873-x1886 A-C Art (Box 1176)
  - x1886 D-Z - x1896 Art (Box 1177)
  - x1897-x1908 Art (Box 1178)
  - x1909-x1916 Art (Box 1179)
  - x1917-x1926 A-M Art (Box 1180)
  - x1926 N-Z - x1928 A-G Art (Box 1181)
  - x1928 H-Z - x1930 A-I Art (Box 1182)
  - x1930 J-Z - x1931 A-T Art (Box 1183)
  - x1931 V-Z - x1933 A-J Art (Box 1184)
  - x1933 K-Z - x1935 A-H Art (Box 1185)
  - x1935 J-Z - x1937 A-F Art (Box 1186)
  - x1937 G-Z - x1939 A-E Art (Box 1187)
  - x1939 F-Z - x1941 A-J Art (Box 1188)
  - x1941 K-Z - x1945 Art (Box 1189)
  - x1949-x1949 (Box 1190)
  - Special Art A-Z (Box 1191)
  - 1950-1954 (Box 1192)
  - Drama 1950-1954 (Box 1193)
- Forestry, Series XI
  For the Classes 1902 to 1949, each year is divided into two sections for graduate and non-graduate files. Files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 1194-1213]
  Files for graduates and non-graduates (1950-1954) are filed together according to year. [Box 1213]
  - 1902-1904 A-Ca (Box 1194)
  - 1904 Chi-Z - 1905 A-L (Box 1195)
  - 1905 M-Z - 1906 A-R (Box 1196)
  - 1906 S-Z - 1907 A-E (Box 1197)
  - 1907 F-Z - 1909 A-F (Box 1198)
  - 1909 G-Z - 1911 A-F (Box 1199)
  - 1911 G-Z - 1912 A-R (Box 1200)
  - 1912 S-Z - 1915 A-G (Box 1201)
  - 1915 H-Z - 1918 (Box 1202)
  - 1919-1923 A-G (Box 1203)